Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What information do we collect?

When using or visiting our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, group information, cultural answers to test questions, or other details. When do we collect information? We collect information from you when you respond to a survey, fill out a form answering test questions or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, answer a survey, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To personalize user's experience.
* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
* To quickly process your transactions.
* To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
* To perform cultural research from the answers to test questions.

### How do we protect visitor information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. We use an SSL certificate. We implement security measures when a user places an order and/or enters, submits, or accesses their information. We use a payment gateway provider.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders.

### Third Party Disclosure

We may transfer your non-identifiable information to third parties. We may also transfer your identifiable information, but only to trusted third parties with a direct affiliation. Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future. Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. [See more](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en)

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action - should a data breach occur we will notify the users via email within 14 business days. We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### Research Use of Inputted Data

By answering questions, you agree the information and data you input can be used for social and cultural research and referenced in published articles or books in the future. The data will always be presented in a generic and anonymous manner.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact info@TheCultureTest.com.

@2024 The Culture Test [Privacy](http://theculturetest.com/privacy) [Terms](http://theculturetest.com/terms) [Write Us](mailto:info@theculturetest.com)
